https://www.magnetone.com.sg/privacy

Privacy Policy
Brands
Canon Fuji Xerox Kyocera Ricoh Xerox View All
Models
Canon IR 2535/2545 Toner Fuji Xerox DC-900/1100 Toner 1KG Kyocera Taskalfa 1800/2200 Toner Ricoh Aficio MP 9000 Toner Xerox WC-5645/5655 Toner 1KG View All
Brands
Canon Fuji Xerox Konica Minolta Ricoh Sharp View All
Models
Canon IR 1600/2000 OPC Drum Canon IR 1730/1740 OPC Drum (Long Life) Canon IR 2016/2020 OPC Drum (Long Life) Canon IR 2200/3300 OPC Drum (Silencer) Canon IR 2270/3570 OPC Drum (Premium-Silencer) View All
Brands
Canon Fuji Xerox Kyocera Ricoh Samsung View All
Models
Canon IR 1018/1022 Toner Cartridge Canon IR 1730/1740 Toner Cartridge Canon IR 2002 Toner Cartridge Canon IR 2016/2020 Toner Cartridge Canon IR 2520/2525 Toner Cartridge View All
Brands
Konica Minolta Kyocera Lexmark Ricoh Xerox View All
Models
Konica Minolta Bizhub 223/283 Feeder Separation Roller Assembly (Genuine) Konica Minolta BIZHUB C224/284 Doc Feeder (Adf) Separation Roller Assembly (Genuine) Konica Minolta Bizhub C224/284 Paper Feed Roller (Genuine) Konica Minolta Bizhub Pro 1050 Paper Feed Roller (Genuine) Konica Minolta Bizhub Pro 920/950 Paper Feed Roller (Genuine) View All
Brands
Canon Fuji Xerox Samsung Xerox Konica Minolta View All
Models
Canon IR ADV C-5030/5035 Carrier 10KG Canon IR ADV C-5045/5051 Carrier 10KG Fuji Xerox DC-236/286 Carrier 200GM Fuji Xerox DC-900/1100 Developer 750GM Fuji Xerox DC-C5540/6550 Carrier 10KG View All
Brands
Canon Fuji Xerox Xerox View All
Models
Canon IR C-2880/3380 Drum Rebuild Kit Fuji Xerox DC-C5540/6550 CYM Drum Rebuild Kit Fuji Xerox DC-IV C2260/2263 Drum Rebuild Kit (CYMK) Fuji Xerox DC-IV C2270/3370 Drum Rebuild Kit (CYMK) Xerox 700 DCP CYM Drum Rebuild Kit View All
Brands
Canon Fuji Xerox Lexmark Oce Ricoh View All
Models
Canon IR 1600/2000 Wiper Blade Canon IR 2016/2020 Wiper Blade Canon IR 2200/3300 Wiper Blade Canon IR 2270/3570 Wiper Blade Canon IR 2520/2525 Wiper Blade View All
Brands
Lexmark Fuji Xerox Xerox Canon Ricoh View All
Models
Lexmark Optra T-630/632 Developer Roller (New Generation) Lexmark Optra T-640/642 Developer Roller (New Generation) Lexmark Optra T-650/652 Developer Roller Fuji Xerox DC-IV C2270/3370 Foam Cleaning Roller Xerox 700 DCP Foam Cleaning Roller View All
Brands
Canon Fuji Xerox Samsung Xerox View All
Models
Canon IR ADV C-3320/3330 Waste Toner Container Canon IR ADV C-5030/5035 Waste Toner Container Canon IR ADV C-5045/5051 Waste Toner Container Fuji Xerox DC-C5540/6550 Waste Toner Container Fuji Xerox DC-III C2200/3300 Waste Toner Container View All
Login
Register
Toner
Colour Toner Mono Toner OPC Drum
Toner Cartridge
Colour Toner Cartridge Mono Toner Cartridge Copier & Printer Parts Developer & Carrier Drum Rebuild Kit
Blades
Wiper Blade Doctor Blade Transfer Belt Blade
Rollers
Developer Roller Primary Charge Roller Magnetic Roller Foam Cleaning Roller Web Roller Fuser Roller Pressure Roller Waste Toner Container
View All
Chips
Cleaning Supplies & Accessories
Chemicals Vacuums Drum Unit Fuser Film Sleeve Transfer Belt
Toner
Colour Toner Mono Toner OPC Drum
Toner Cartridge
Colour Toner Cartridge Mono Toner Cartridge Copier & Printer Parts Developer & Carrier Drum Rebuild Kit
Blades
Wiper Blade Doctor Blade Transfer Belt Blade
Rollers
Developer Roller Primary Charge Roller Magnetic Roller Foam Cleaning Roller Web Roller Fuser Roller Pressure Roller Waste Toner Container
Privacy Policy
Home Privacy Policy
This privacy policy sets out how Magnetone Singapore Pte Ltd uses and protects any information that you provide when you use this website. Magnetone Singapore Pte Ltd is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we request you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. Magnetone Singapore may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You are advised to check this page from time to time. What we collect We may collect the following information:
name and job title contact information including email address demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers
What we do with the information we gather We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:
Internal record keeping. We may use the information to improve our products and services. We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting with the email address which you have provided. From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.
Security We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. How we use cookies A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps to analyse web traffic or informs you when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences. We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us to analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system. Overall, cookies help us to provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website. Links to other websites Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over other websites. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question. Controlling your personal information You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:
whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at info@magnetone.com.sg
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen. If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
